明白了吗
Do you understand?
我们空降后  控制空降区让蓝队撤离
We drop in, clear LZs for Blue Team evacuation.
我们进入城市
We make our way into the city proper.
这些都是废弃建筑
These buildings are abandoned,
但我们得知  这里也有一道旋转门
but we learned there is a turnstile.
可能会遭到双向时间反击
Expect a bitemporal response.
他们有逆时间武器吗
They'll have inverse ordnance?
逆时间的  常规的
Inverse, conventional,
正向对手  逆向对手  他们都有
forward antagonists, inverted antagonists, they have it all.
在城市的另一边
On the other side of the city,
沿着山坡爬上去可以到达爆炸源
the ground rises to the ridge above the hypocenter.
小分队将从市区走这条通道
A splinter unit will take this tunnel from the city
到达山洞里的爆炸源
to the floor of the hypocenter.
蓝队在这里发现了一个入口
Blue Team located an entrance here.